

# Elfar Smári Sverrisson

Address:

Njardargata 39, 101 Reykjavík, Iceland

Phone:

+354 823 6930

Email:

elfar@elfarsmari.com

Website:

www.elfarsmari.com

### **Profile**

My name is Elfar, I'm 27 years old and I've been working as a compositor for more than three years. Over these last years I have grown a lot in my work and acquired new skills, especially during my time working on the feature film "Everest" which is my most challenging project up to date. I have learned to work under a lot of pressure delivering top class work on tight deadlines.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Compositor, RVX

Reykjavík, Iceland — April 2014 - February 2016

- Compositor for TV Series "Trapped"
- Compositor for feature film "Everest"
- Compositor for commercial "Invokana"

## Compositor, Filmgate

Gothenburg, Sweden — June 2013 - April 2014

- Compositor for feature film "Stonehearst Asylum"
- Compositor for feature film "Before I go to sleep"
- Compositor for feature film "Good people"
- Compositor for animated feature "Bamse och tjuvstaden"
- Compositor for TV mini-series "Ettor & Nollor"

### Compositing intern, Filmgate

Gothenburg, Sweden — January 2013 - June 2013

- Compositor for feature film "Diana"
- Compositor for feature film "The hidden child"

#### VFX Supervisor, Maiestic

Reykjavík, Iceland — May 2012 - October 2012

VFX Supervisor and compositor for TV series "Óupplýst"

## **EDUCATION**

### Campus i12 - University of Jönköping, Sweden

Digital Compositor — August 2011 - May 2013

### Multimedia school of Iceland, Iceland

Multimedia designer — August 2009 - May 2011

## Menntaskólinn við Hamrahlíð, Iceland

A-Levels in science — August 2004 - May 2011

### **SKILLS**

My experience and skills include photo real cg integration, matte painting integration, element integration, green screen extraction, 3d projection, nuke particles, paint, roto, Nuke and Linux.

## **REFERENCES**

- Daði Einarsson: Owner and Creative Director at RVX (dadi@rvx.is)
- Sigurjón Garðarsson: Compositing Supervisor at RVX (sigurjon@rvx.is)
- Håkan Blomdahl: Compositing Supervisor and founder at Filmgate (hakan.blomdahl@chimneygroup.com)